[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The vitamins from the B complex have many functions but generally play most important role in which of these processes of the human body?", "correct_answer": "Cell metabolism", "incorrect_answers": ["Cell excretion", "Cell reproduction", "Cell regeneration"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kentucky Fried Movie spoofed space movies like Star Wars and Star Trek.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the self-defense mechanism which allows lizards to break off their tails when captured?", "correct_answer": "Autotomy", "incorrect_answers": ["Apotemnophilia", "Autonomy", "Autism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You will need this type for memory card, if you want to expand yout Nokia 7710.", "correct_answer": "MMC Card", "incorrect_answers": ["XD Memory Card", "SD Memory Card", "Compact Flash Card"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Paul Reubens appears in the movies Up In Smoke, Cheech and Chongs Next Movie  and Nice Dreams.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie did Scarlett Johansson play a character named Katherine Kay Lake?", "correct_answer": "The Black Dahlia", "incorrect_answers": ["A Good Woman", "The Nanny Diaries", "The Spirit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common drink was first named the \u201cEsteemed Brain Tonic and Intellectual Beverage\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Coca Cola", "incorrect_answers": ["Tab", "Dr Pepper", "Sprite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wyoming was the first U. S. state to give women the right to vote.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Darth Vaders superior?", "correct_answer": "Emporer Palpatine", "incorrect_answers": ["Grand Moff Tarkin", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "No One"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sometimes skunks kill domestic animals.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hummus is a popular meal in the Arab world and especially in the Middle East. What does the name of the dish mean?", "correct_answer": "Chickpeas", "incorrect_answers": ["Soil", "Butter", "Food"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mount Erebus is a volcano located on this continent.", "correct_answer": "Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "South America", "Asia"]}]